<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top Mobile MMORPG 2023</string>
    <string name="profile_name">Bima Adityo Kurniawan</string>
    <string name="profile_email">bimaadityokurniawan@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>

    <string-array name="data_game_name">
        <item>Toram Online</item>
        <item>Genshin Impact</item>
        <item>Tower of Fantasy</item>
        <item>MapleStory M - Fantasy MMORPG</item>
        <item>Dragon Raja</item>
        <item>Black Desert Mobile</item>
        <item>Rucoy Online - MMORPG MMO RPG</item>
        <item>GrowStone Online: pixel MMORPG</item>
        <item>SimpleMMO (MMORPG - PVP - RPG)</item>
        <item>AdventureQuest 3D MMO RPG</item>
        <item>Alchemia Story - MMORPG</item>
        <item>Summoners War: Chronicles</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_game_icon">
        <item>@drawable/toramonline</item>
        <item>@drawable/genshinimpact</item>
        <item>@drawable/toweroffantasy</item>
        <item>@drawable/maplestorym</item>
        <item>@drawable/dragonraja</item>
        <item>@drawable/blackdesertmobile</item>
        <item>@drawable/rucoyonline</item>
        <item>@drawable/growstone</item>
        <item>@drawable/simplemmo</item>
        <item>@drawable/adventurequest</item>
        <item>@drawable/alchemiastory</item>
        <item>@drawable/summonerswarchronicles</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_publisher">
        <item>Asobimo, Inc.</item>
        <item>COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD.</item>
        <item>Level Infinite</item>
        <item>NEXON Company</item>
        <item>Archosaur Games</item>
        <item>PEARL ABYSS</item>
        <item>RicardoGzz</item>
        <item>SUPERCAT</item>
        <item>Galahad Creative</item>
        <item>Artix Entertainment LLC</item>
        <item>Asobimo, Inc.</item>
        <item>Com2uS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_rating">
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>4.4</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>4.3</item>
        <item>4.3</item>
        <item>4.1</item>
        <item>4.7</item>
        <item>4.2</item>
        <item>4.8</item>
        <item>4.3</item>
        <item>3.9</item>
        <item>3.8</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_review_count">
        <item>999K reviews</item>
        <item>4.36M reviews</item>
        <item>184K reviews</item>
        <item>115K reviews</item>
        <item>198K reviews</item>
        <item>429K reviews</item>
        <item>243K reviews</item>
        <item>96.4K reviews</item>
        <item>25.8K reviews</item>
        <item>81K reviews</item>
        <item>59.3K reviews</item>
        <item>29.1K reviews</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_game_total_downloads">
        <item>10000000</item>
        <item>50000000</item>
        <item>5000000</item>
        <item>5000000</item>
        <item>5000000</item>
        <item>10000000</item>
        <item>5000000</item>
        <item>1000000</item>
        <item>1000000</item>
        <item>1000000</item>
        <item>1000000</item>
        <item>1000000</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="data_game_minimum_os">
        <item>Android 7.0</item>
        <item>Android 5.0</item>
        <item>Android 7.0</item>
        <item>Android 5.1</item>
        <item>Android 5.0</item>
        <item>Android 5.0</item>
        <item>Android 4.1</item>
        <item>Android 5.0</item>
        <item>Android 5.0</item>
        <item>Android 5.1</item>
        <item>Android 4.4</item>
        <item>Android 8.0</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_released_on">
        <item>Jul 9, 2015</item>
        <item>Sep 26, 2020</item>
        <item>Aug 7, 2022</item>
        <item>May 28, 2018</item>
        <item>July 18, 2019</item>
        <item>Dec 8, 2019</item>
        <item>Feb 20, 2016</item>
        <item>May 17, 2017</item>
        <item>Feb 3, 2018</item>
        <item>Oct 19, 2016</item>
        <item>Jun 12, 2018</item>
        <item>Nov 3, 2022</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_last_updated">
        <item>Sep 28, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 17, 2023</item>
        <item>Aug 30, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 14, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 4, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 22, 2023</item>
        <item>Oct 4, 2023</item>
        <item>Feb 16, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 4, 2023</item>
        <item>Oct 2, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 7, 2023</item>
        <item>Sep 27, 2023</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_game_description">

        <item>
            ★ Popular MMORPG hitting 13 million downloads worldwide!\n\n    Unrestricted character creations!\n\n    With more than 500 billion combinations available, feel free to create your own character to your liking!\n\n    Sword? Magic? Anything you like!\n\n    “Profession,“ which is often the case with MMORPG, does not exist in Toram. Sword? (Magic) Staff? Bow? Halberd? Feel free to decide your own fighting style!\n\n    Build &amp; Train your character to your heart’s content!\n\n    Equipped with a “Skill Tree“ system enabling players to enhance and strengthen their characters as they wish.\n    Create combos and discover your own battle style!\n\n    Changeable weapons and equipment color!\n\n    You can color your favorite weapon with the color you like when you obtain equipment with a “Color Info“!\n    Moreover, you can freely create the abilities of your equipment as you proceed further with the game…!\n\n    Go on an adventure with your friends across the country!\n\n    RPG (MMORPG) that can be played and connects you with your friends online across the country!\n    The powerful monster that you fail to beat on your own could possibly be knocked down by forming a party with your friends! Let’s explore the vast and beautiful 3D world with many friends!\n\n    Party play even by yourself!\n\n    You can even enjoy party play when you are playing alone by borrowing and battling together with other player’s character known as “mercenary“ or by summoning a “partner“ from your own sub-characters!\n\n    【Story Setting】\n\n    Decades ago, the world was hit by a devastating catastrophe, crumbling the ground into pieces. The gods quickly gathered the pieces scattered in all directions and hurriedly put them together. The result, a bizarre looking world resembling a mosaic.\n    The nation that was originally there had ceased to exist. As a result of repeated clashes of principles and interests among the 4 tribes, the people split into 4 factions.\n    At such times, an adventurer (you) came to this peculiar world.\n    The adventurer (you) goes through a series of adventures while meeting various people belonging to the 4 factions in the world to confront the secretly proliferating mysteries behind it.\n\n    【Game Outline】\n    Title: RPG Toram Online - MMORPG\n    Genre: MMORPG with complete freedom\n\n    *MMORPG: Massively Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game\n\n    Recommended Requirements\n\n    OS : Android 9 or later\n    SoC : Snapdragon 720G / 845 or higher\n    RAM : 4GB or higher\n    Internet Connection : Wi-Fi (Upload / Download 10 Mbps or more)\n\n    Service performance and availability are not guaranteed when\n    ・Devices do not meet the recommended system requirements\n    ・Devices are no longer supported by the manufacturers or retailers\n    ・Apps not supported by the manufacturers or retailers are being used on your device\n    ・Apps that root your device are being used\n    ・Virtual machines or emulators are being used\n    ・VPN(Virtual Private Network) is being used\n    ・SoC is not compatible with 64-bit\n    ・The app is not installed in the internal storage on your device\n    ・SAMSUNG Galaxy series are being used to run the app (due to the screen glitches occurring on these devices)\n    ・The beta version of the Operating System is being used\n\n    *Only the Android devices powered by the Snapdragon series SoC from Qualcomm Inc. are supported.\n    *A bigger amount of RAM than that stated in the recommended system requirements may be required depending on your device resolution.\n\n    Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/toram.jp\n\n    Please go to “Contact Us“ in the app in order to submit a request or report a bug.\n    Inquiries received directly from the app will be prioritized.
        </item>

        <item>
            Step into Teyvat, a vast world teeming with life and flowing with elemental energy.\n\n    You and your sibling arrived here from another world. Separated by an unknown god, stripped of your powers, and cast into a deep slumber, you now awake to a world very different from when you first arrived.\n\n    Thus begins your journey across Teyvat to seek answers from The Seven — the gods of each element. Along the way, prepare to explore every inch of this wondrous world, join forces with a diverse range of characters, and unravel the countless mysteries that Teyvat holds…\n\n    MASSIVE OPEN WORLD\n\n    Climb any mountain, swim across any river, and glide over the world below, taking in the jaw-dropping scenery each step of the way. And if you stop to investigate a wandering Seelie or strange mechanism, who knows what you might discover?\n\n    ELEMENTAL COMBAT SYSTEM\n\n    Harness the seven elements to unleash elemental reactions. Anemo, Electro, Hydro, Pyro, Cryo, Dendro, and Geo interact in all sorts of ways, and Vision wielders have the power to turn this to their advantage.\n\n    Will you vaporize Hydro with Pyro, electro-charge it with Electro, or freeze it with Cryo? Your mastery of the elements will give you the upper hand in battle and exploration.\n\n    BEAUTIFUL VISUALS\n\n    Feast your eyes on the world around you, with a stunning art style, real-time rendering, and finely tuned character animations delivering you a truly immersive visual experience. Lighting and weather all change naturally over time, bringing every detail of this world to life.\n\n    SOOTHING SOUNDTRACK\n\n    Let the beautiful sounds of Teyvat draw you in as you explore the expansive world around you. Performed by the world`s top orchestras such as London Philharmonic Orchestra and Shanghai Symphony Orchestra, the soundtrack changes seamlessly with the time and gameplay to match the mood.\n\n    BUILD YOUR DREAM TEAM\n\n    Team up with a diverse cast of characters in Teyvat, each with their own unique personalities, stories, and abilities. Discover your favorite party combinations and level up your characters to help you conquer even the most daunting of enemies and domains.\n\n    JOURNEY WITH FRIENDS\n\n    Team up with friends across various platforms to trigger more elemental action, tackle tricky boss fights, and conquer challenging domains together to reap rich rewards.\n\n    As you stand atop the peaks of Jueyun Karst and take in the rolling clouds and vast terrain stretching out before you, you may wish to stay in Teyvat a little longer. But until you are reunited with your lost sibling, how can you rest? Go forth, Traveler, and begin your adventure!\n\n    SUPPORT\n    If you encounter any issues during the game, you can send us feedback via the in-game Customer Service Center.\n   Official Site: https://genshin.hoyoverse.com/\n    Forums: https://www.hoyolab.com/\n    Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/Genshinimpact/\n    Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/genshinimpact/\n    Twitter: https://twitter.com/GenshinImpact\n    YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/c/GenshinImpact\n    Discord: https://discord.gg/genshinimpact\n    Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Genshin_Impact/
        </item>

        <item>
            Embark together on your fantasy adventure!\n\nSet hundreds of years in the future on the distant planet of Aida, the shared open-world MMORPG, anime-infused sci-fi adventure Tower of Fantasy from developer Hotta Studio and publisher Level Infinite, is now available on PC and mobile platforms globally. Players will be able to experience an anime-inspired post-apocalyptic sci-fi art style, freeform character development, and exciting combat through thrilling battles and exciting open-world exploration.\n\nIn Tower of Fantasy, dwindling resources and a lack of energy have forced mankind to leave earth and migrate to Aida, a lush and habitable alien world. There, they observed the comet Mara and discovered an unknown but powerful energy called “Omnium“ contained in it. They built the Omnium Tower to capture Mara, but due to the influence of Omnium radiation, a catastrophic disaster occurred on their new homeworld.\n\nImmersive Open-World\nExperience a vast alien world full of beautiful open vistas and imposing futuristic structures.\n\nUnique Characters\nWield the unique weapons of each character that grant different gameplay styles as you explore their compelling backstories.\n\nGrow and Explore Together\nParty up with friends online and take on new adventures in the shared open world.\n\nEpic Combat\nEngage in epic battles against enemies of all shapes and sizes as you switch weapons and gameplay styles on the fly to unlock your own personal fighting style.\n\nExplore and Interact\nExplore and interact with a vibrant living world as you discover your own journey through it.\n\nTo learn more about Tower of Fantasy, go to https://toweroffantasy-global.com or check out our other official channels:\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/Tower.of.Fantasy.Official\nInstagram: https://www.instagram.com/@toweroffantasy_official\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/ToF_EN_Official\nYouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC!NbDLZjc41RQk-pV94mu_A/about\nDiscord: https://discord.gg/eDgkQJ4aYe
        </item>

        <item>
            Looking for MapleStory nostalgia with a twist? Try MapleStory M!\nMapleStory M brings the nostalgic world of MapleStory to your mobile device. Enjoy an authentic fantasy MMORPG experience whenever and wherever you want, right in the palm of your hand.\n\n▶ Hold Maple World in the palm of your hand!◀\nWhen you want to visit Maple World, but you just can’t find the time, don’t worry! MapleStory M is here to save your day!\n☞ Relive the good ol’ days in popular locales like Henesys, Kerning City, and more!\n☞ From classic MapleStory characters, like Dark Knight and Bishop, to the latest and greatest, like Cannoneer and Pathfinder, MapleStory M has you covered with nonstop updates!\n\n▶ Fashion is key in MapleStory!◀\nTired of your character looking the same as everyone else?\nNot in Maple World!\nTake advantage of Royal Plastic Surgery, Mix Dye, and more to customize your character to the max!\n\n▶ Take advantage of endless growth and Trade Station systems!◀\nAre you a diehard, but value a good nap as much as the next player? Look no further!\n☞ In Maple M World, Auto-Battles don’t stop, even if you close the game!\n☞ Find crucial items at the Trade Station and use them to grow stronger than ever!\n\n▶ Go beyond the basic questline!◀\nDo you love completing quests, but find yourself wanting more?\nIn Maple World, you can catch monsters and cook!\n☞ Star Force Field: Ready to enhance your equipment and take down stronger monsters? This is the perfect place to level up!\n☞ Kerning M Tower: Assemble a team of your best characters and fight your way to the top.\n☞ Guild: Team up with your friends to complete Guild Dungeons and Guild Elite Battles!\n☞ Pet: Hoping for more than one pet? You can take on adventures in Maple World with three pets!\n☞ Expeditions &amp; Commanders: Join a party to fight all kinds of bosses, each with a unique attack pattern!\n\nBut that`s not all! MapleStory M has a variety of seasonal events and rewards just for you!\nReturn to the fantasy world of MapleStory – download MapleStory M today!\n\n■ Support &amp; Community\nAre you having problems? Contact our 1:1 Support in-game or send us an inquiry at\nhelp_MapleStoryM@nexon.com\n\n[For the best gaming experience, MapleStory M requires OS 5.0, CPU dual-core and RAM 1.5GB or higher. Some devices under the specification may have difficulties running the game.]\n\nFollow us on our official communities to get the latest news and updates!\nFacebook: http://www.facebook.com/PlayMapleM\n\nTerms of Service: http://m.nexon.com/terms/304\nPrivacy Policy: http://m.nexon.com/terms/305\n\n■ App Permissions Information\nIn order to provide the following services, we are requesting certain permissions.\n\n[Mandatory Access Rights]\nSave picture/media/file: game installation file, save update file and attach screenshots for customer service\n\n[Optional Permission]\nPhone: Allow your phone number to be collected for promotional text messages\nMicrophone: To enable voice chat during the game\nNotifications: Allow the app to send service notifications.\nBluetooth: Required to communicate with nearby Bluetooth devices.\n※ This authorization only applies to certain countries, so numbers may not be collected from all players.\n\n[How to withdraw access rights]\n▶ Android 6.0 or higher: Settings > Applications > Select App > Permissions\n▶ Under Android 6.0: Update OS version to retract permissions; Uninstall app\n※ If the app does not ask you to grant your permission, manage your permissions by following by the above steps.
        </item>

        <item>
            Diversified Classes Welcome a New Member - 14th Class Yasai Debuts!\nInspired by Japanese ninjas, Yasai wields a huge folding fan as a melee weapon and is equipped with the traditional ninja weapon Kunai for long-range attacks. With cool skills and exquisite weapons, Yasai is ready to unleash your inner ninja!\n\nThe Brand-new PVP Mode- Phantom Tracking is now live!\nUnlike traditional competitive PVP modes, Phantom Tracking is incredibly engaging and unique. Hide and Seek between two opposing camps. Whether you choose pursuers or pretenders, the fun never stops! If you are a pretender, remember to stay still and be careful not to be caught by your opponents!\n\nSTUNNING GRAPHICS\nPowered by Unreal Engine 4, Dragon Raja is a next-generation open world mobile game that offers a gigantic, immersive world through the use of cutting-edge technology and stunning graphics. The game uses a simulated physical collision system and optical motion capture technology to deliver a “smart” in-game environment that offers players the ultimate gaming experience. Its fantastic graphics can mistake people into thinking they’re playing a PC game!\n\nNEW STORIES, NEW CHALLENGES\nFrom Tokyo to Siberia, countless scenic landmarks all over the world have been seamlessly integrated into the game’s open storyline. In-game NPCs offer separate quests or have different dialogue depending on what choices players make, giving them the power to change the game’s world. And now, players can experience new stories, challenge more powerful world bosses, and embark on a brand new journey!\n\nCOMPREHENSIVE CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION\nDragon Raja features a comprehensive character customization system. Players can define their characters’ personalities depending on their responses to unforeseen events. In Dragon Raja, unique characters can be created and dressed up however players choose, with endless customization. Casual, retro, street, and futuristic are just a few of the styles that can be chosen from when styling characters, with additional styles soon to come!\n\nSTORY\nThe Dragon Lord, once sealed away by a race of humans known as Hybrids, has come back to life. The Hybrids—humans gifted with superpowers—are gathering to prepare for the coming battle, which is sure to be an epic showdown.\n\nTo support the high game quality and massive game content, Dragon Raja is a relatively large file. Please note that 3GB of game files are needed to download the core game, and another 1.5GB of art files need to be downloaded after entering the game.\n\nDevice Compatibility:\nSystem version: Android 5.0 or above\nRAM: 2GB or more\nStorage space: at least 6GB\nCPU: Qualcomm Snapdragon 660 or higher\n\nSNS\nOfficial site: https://dragonraja.archosaur.com/\nDiscord: https://discord.com/invite/KGN63W3jrp\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/DragonRajaEN\nVK: https://vk.com/dragonrajamobilegame\nYouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@dragonrajaglobal
        </item>

        <item>
            THE WORLD CLASS MMORPG 『Black Desert Mobile』\n\n    Are you an MMORPG player enthusiastic for adventures and combat?\n    “Black Desert“ is a global MMORPG played by 40 million worldwide.\n    Experience what a real MMORPG is on mobile.\n    We invite you to take a step into the world of Black Desert Mobile\n    to experience the adventure of your dreams.\n\n    [Black Desert Mobile FEATURES]\n\n    ■ Story of BLACK DESERT\n    An Adventurer who’s lost all memories stands at the center of a continent to unravel the truth about the ancients. Begin your journey to uncover the truth of this world.\n    Explore the wide world and create your own story.\n\n    ■ Incredible Graphics on Mobile &amp; Breathtaking Action\n    Experience immersive graphics and an innovative combat system.\n    Enjoy a gameplay experience with action-packed, satisfying combat.\n\n    ■ My Personal Camp &amp; Life Skills\n    You can also enjoy trading, fishing, alchemy, gathering, and more\n    as you manage your own camp.\n\n    ■ Create the character of your dreams\n    Customize your character through Black Desert Mobile’s unique customization system.\n\n    ■ PVP Contents\n    Join a guild to enjoy the PvP content, Siege Wars, and Node Wars!\n    Be victorious with your guild members!\n    You can also enjoy enthralling 1 vs 1 live matches with other Adventurers.\n\n    ** To the Black Desert Mobile Adventurers who begin their long journey…\n    On your adventure, you may encounter hardships and struggle to overcome them at times.\n    But I am sure you`ll find yourself enjoying the adventure as you complete each of the quests.\n    Begin your journey in the MMORPG of your dreams!\n\n    [Black Desert Mobile Official Website]\n    https://www.world.blackdesertm.com\n\n    [Minimum RAM Requirements]\n    3GB\n\n    ■ App Access\n    We require permission to provide the following services while you use the app.\n\n    [Optional Permissions]\n    Storage: Access to storage required to write forum posts and upload photos.\n\n    [How to Change Permissions]\n    ▶ Android 6.0 or higher: Settings > Apps > Select Permission Settings > Permissions > Set to allow or deny\n    ▶ Below Android 6.0: Upgrade the operating system to change settings, or delete the app\n    ※ The app may not provide other options to change permissions itself but can always be done with the above method.\n    ※ If the operating system is a version lower than Android 6.0, then you cannot change permission settings for individual apps. We recommend upgrading to 6.0 or higher.\n    ※ If you deny permission for required access, it could disrupt resources or make you unable to login to the game
        </item>

        <item>
            Rucoy Online is a Massively Multiplayer Online Role Playing Game where you can fight monsters with your friends in it’s real time open world.\n\nFeatures:\n√ Player vs Player (PvP)\n√ Guild System\n√ Play as a Knight, Archer or Mage\n√ You can change your character class anytime\n√ Use spells to deal more damage\n√ Ally with other players and form a team to defeat strong monsters and get extra experience\n√ Hunt dozens of different monsters\n√ Find the best equipment\n√ Increase your level and skills without limits\n√ Ever growing open world\n√ Chat with other players\n√ Customize your character\n√ No account registration, just link your character to your Google account and that’s it\n\nHow to play:\n- To move touch where you want to go\n- To attack simply select a target\n- Use the buttons on the left side to restore health, mana or use a special ability\n- Use the buttons on the right to change weapons\n- To pick up loot from the ground just touch the hand icon\n- Each level increases your health points, mana points, moving speed, attack and defense\n\nPvP system:\n- Attacking and/or killing innocent players will mark you as cursed\n- Attacking and/or killing cursed players won`t mark you as cursed\n- There is a gold reward for killing cursed players\n- Standing on a PvP zone will reduce the duration of your curse\n\nWebsite: www.rucoyonline.com\nFacebook: https://www.facebook.com/rucoyonlineofficial\nReddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/RucoyOnline/\nTwitter: https://twitter.com/RucoyOnline
        </item>

        <item>
            ■■■ 2d online MMORPG game to find the legendary stone! ■■■\n\nWelcome to Grow Stone Online, adventure to find the legendary stone!\nPlay 2d pixel mmorpg games and Grow stone with multiplayers online!\nWhy stone? Cause it’s the first weapon of man in the world!!\n\n[How to Play]\n○ Super Easy! Just tap and Touch, That’s it\n○ If you’re busy, Use Auto Function!\n○ Get Rewards while you’re not in game\n○ Jump up and use mining machine!\n\n[Best Weapon]\n○ Knife? Bomb? Arrow? what about stone?\n○ Dig and grow stone in mine! do IDLE RPG\n○ Imagine what happened if you combine them\n○ Make a Pheonix, Solar Stones etc\n\n[Enjoy 2d MMORPG]\n○ Fight in Dangerous Dungeon games with friends\n○ Be Brave! Adventure to Tower of challenge\n○ Anyone who fight with me? Let’s PVP!\n○ Enjoy Castle Battle with your clan\n○ Run! it’s a Battle Field! Co-op!\n○ Hunt Monsters in many fields, do RPG!\n○ Exciting Raid-Boss monster online\n○ Challenge! The hardest hell mode of dungeon!\n○ Show me your power! Let’s fight in Arena\n○ Get Fishing Bait back! Catch Flying Fishes now\n\n[More friends, More fun]\n○ Join the clan and be the best clan!\n○ You`re not alone! Enjoy Party Hunting!\n○ Exciting Party Quest! Real RPG!\n○ Become a couple with couple system~ xoxo\n○ Doing fishing, talking with others, get items too\n○ Trade at town, mine by vending machine!\n\n[So attractive]\n○ Meet various Avatar, pet in 2d pixel, retro graphic\n○ Decorate your avatar with armor, accessory etc\n○ Time killing! addictive Combination! like a IDLE games!\n○ Enjoy rain, snow! weather just like a real world.\n\n[EVENT]\n○ Free Dungeon Tickets everyday!\n○ Double Gold, Rubies in `Hot time`!\n○ Got tons of gift from `On Time` Event!\n○ Rain will bring you good luck\n○ More amazing event is waiting for you!\n\n[Contact us]\n○ Please send mail if you have any question or find any errors or love our game.\nWe`ll try to reply as soon as possible even though we are on the adventure.\n\nWaiting for you, Brave Adventurers!\nSee you in 2d pixel mmorpg game, Grow Stone Online!\n\n○ Community here : https://www.facebook.com/GrowStoneGlob/\n○ Customer Service : https://bit.ly/supercat_cs_en (we@supercat.co.kr)\n○ Terms of Service : https://www.supercat.co.kr/terms?lang=en\n■■■ Thank you! ■■■
        </item>

        <item>
            Join over 700,000 players and enjoy the best MMORPG experience in the simplest way. Our tiny MMO game features medieval inspired pixel art graphics with quintessential RPG components. It is an incremental RPG with MMO elements at its very core. All you need to do is take a step with a simple click of a button and away you go!\n\nSimple, yet deep MMO experience\nTraverse the world with strange, funny, serious, and downright ridiculous adventure texts with every step that you take. Duel other players, find legendary loot, team up and attack world bosses, join a guild, perform quests, become a market trader, converse with the community, become a hitman, and much much more! The choices are endless!\n\nFeatures -\n✔︎ Duel fellow players in the battle arena and find out who is the strongest (PvP).\n✔︎ Traverse through the crazy world of SimpleMMO with just a press of a button.\n✔︎ Partake in epic quests, tasks and team together to defeat extremely powerful world bosses.\n✔︎ Find over 8,000 different pieces of loot on your adventures.\n✔︎ Level up your character in this strange and funky world so that you become incredibly powerful.\n✔︎ Start a job and become a guard, thief, master chef, blacksmith, and much more.\n✔︎ Engage with the community and compete against them in the leaderboards.\n✔︎ Join guilds and help your fellow guild members in giant-scale guild battles.\n✔︎ Join forces with enemies and friends to defeat world bosses.\n✔︎︎ Customisable RPG characters that allow you to change your appearance.\n\nAwesome events and an active community\nWith frequent events and an incredibly active, and friendly, community. The spark that ignites the fires of SimpleMMO will never diminish. There is always something that will keep you entertained.\n\nWho is this game for?\n✔︎ Fan of clicking, text based MMORPG games.\n✔︎ Fans of incremental games.\n✔︎ RPG fanatics.\n✔︎ People who like loot based games.\n✔︎ People who want to play the perfect game while they are on the toilet at work.\n✔︎ People who don`t take life too seriously.\n✔︎ People.\n\nWhether you like nostalgic RPG games, or graphically intensive fully-fledged MMORPG games, you should try SimpleMMO. It’s addictive, exciting, and most of all…it`s simple!\n\nA truly minimal MMO experience\nWe aim to provide you with a very deep incremental RPG under the veneer of a extremely simple user experience. We have worked hard so that all of your favourite archetypal MMORPG features can be played in the simplest way. Get experience, grow your character, and even continue your progress when you are not playing by using our idle-like features.\n\n➤ Unique and Highly Rated\nPlayed in over 150 countries, and more than 400,00 registered players.\n\nSimpleMMO takes online text-based MMORPGs to the next level and provides it in a very simple and seamless way. It can be as casual or as hardcore as you want it to be.\n\nWe hope you love our game as much as our players do! Install it today and let us know what you think.\n\nInstall this incredibly fun and addicting incremental MMORPG game today and let us know what you think!\n\n[Social Media]\n■ Instagram: https://www.facebook.com/simplemmo\n■ Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/simplemmo\n■ Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/simplemmogame\n\nFor support queries, please email simplemmo@galahadcreative.com\n\nDownload now and start your adventure!
        </item>

        <item>
            This MMORPG is a little bit different… you’ve been warned. Adventure Quest 3D is a growing online world where you can be anyone or anything you want. Battle monsters as a Mage. Change Classes anytime. Craft items, swords, and fidget spinners. Fish with friends. Or crush ‘em all in 5v5 PvP. Adopt a weird looking cat called a Moglin. And explore the vast open world as… a bush. AQ3D is pretty much the metaverse before the metaverse was a thing.\n\nEpic quests of adventure… and some really strange stuff… await thee in Adventure Quest 3D!\n\nSORCERER GENERAL’S WARNING\nThis game is ONLY for fans of fantasy MMO open world games, passionately involved game developers, and heroes who wandered here by mistake but downloaded AdventureQuest and loved it anyway. May contain Artix’s unpredictable tongue-in-cheek humor, parody, puns, memes, dad jokes, and oddly-fused monsters (Werepyres?). AQ3D is so casually hard core that there is a 99% chance you will die before the game even begins. But maybe you’ll get lucky and DEATH (aka The Grim Reaper) will make you a deal you can’t refuse. Seems legit. Probably safe.\n\nNOT PAY-TO-WIN\n• Finally, an MMO that’s not going to wreck your wallet\n• Earn power &amp; cool items through gameplay. Wow, what a concept!\n• Optional cosmetics if you’d like to support us… and our anime obsession ^_^\n\nSPECIAL EVENTS\n• Epic in-game events &amp; weird holidays (Taco Day!)\n• Battleon town changes to reflect seasons (not taco seasonings)\n• Exclusive items and wild souvenirs\n\nFREE DLC\n• We’re literally building new game elements for you right now\n• Join us for weekly-ish releases\n\nAQ3D IS TRUE CROSS PLATFORM\n• Play your character from anywhere\n• Yes, all devices log into the same world\n• Yes, you can switch to your phone and take it to the potty and then go back to playing on your computer\n• No, you should not drag your gaming desktop into the bathroom\n\nTHE BEST MMORPG VILLAINS &amp; MONSTERS\n• Our bad guys can beat up your other game’s bad guys\n• Necro Knights\n• Vampires Lords\n• Werewolf Gladiators\n• Pirates vs Ninjas\n• DEATH - Underworld Celebrity\n• Frogzards (a frog + a ???)\n• Drickens - half Dragon, half chicken\n• Lots of Dragons\n• OMG why do we love Dragons so much?\n\nCUSTOMIZE YOUR CHARACTER\n• Make a unique hero and look any way you want\n• Equip any item for power or appearance\n• Axes, swords, staffs, sundried fish, scythe blades (scythe + sword = awesome), fidget spinners (why did you make us do this?), pew pew thingies, sleek suits, old school knight armor, matrixy-looking long coats, gloves, boots, capes, helms, belts, hair, and accessories (make an impact with skull hair clips; so hot right now)\n\nMULTI-CLASS: PLAY THE WAY YOU WANT\n• Collect Classes like Necromancer, Paladin, Dragon Slayer, Rogue, and Warrior\n• Switch between Classes at any time\n• Rank up Classes, unlock Cross Skills, and become one of our legends!\n\nPARKOUR CHALLENGE MAPS\nYou will regret that we let you jump in this game XD Some of our parkour maps are 100% evil. LAZORS!\n\nFAST TRAVEL FORMS\n• Over 200 travel forms and growing\n• Transform into birds, dragons, and creatures that move at high speed\n• Except the bush transformation… awkward\n\nDUNGEONS, RAIDS, &amp; BOSS FIGHT CHALLENGES\n• 20 player raid (like the Dragon`s Lair)\n• 5 player dungeons\n• 2 player adventure… date night?\n• Solo - just like when I went to dances in school\n• Or just roam a world full of players looking for trouble\n\nCURRENT FEATURES\n• Battle Monsters in Real-time Combat\n• Summon &amp; Teleport to your Friends\n• 100% hypoallergenic Pets\n• Crafting\n• Tons of things to complain about!\n• PvP\n• Bad puns\n• Cutscenes you won’t want to skip! (Probably)\n\nSTALK… erm, FOLLOW US FOR ALL THE AQ3D MADNESS!\n\nOFFICIAL SITE: https://www.AQ3D.com\nTWITTER: @ArtixKrieger or https://twitter.com/artixkrieger/\nFACEBOOK: https://www.facebook.com/AdventureQuest3D/\nDISCORD: https://discord.com/invite/FQsFCGV
        </item>

        <item>
            ◆Design your character freely!◆\nCreate the character you really want!\nAdjust your character’s hairstyle, height, body structure, eyebrow length, eye color and more!\n\n\n◆You are not alone, explore with YOME◆\nExplore with the help of “YOME“!\nYOME will quide you to your destination, support you in battles and help with synthesizing items!\nCustomize your YOME like your character, and create your ideal partner!\n\n\n◆Solo-Player Mode◆\nUse the Solo Player Mode feature to play by yourself!\nIf you feel you wouldn’t fit in with MMORPG community, it’s okay!\nUse this mode to play more casually by yourself!\n\n\n◆Easy communication with Like and Stickers!◆\nSend a “Like“ for those players who you want to be friends with!\nAlso, “Sticker“ function will make communication faster and easier!\nLet’s make many friends!\n\n\n◆Battle hard with easy commands!◆\nSimply choose your commands to fight!\nCooperate with your “YOME“ and defeat the enemies!\nChallenge the strong enemies with your friends! Maximum of 8 players can join the battle!\n\n\n◆Unforgettable story and characters!◆\nYou will be able to join in this fantastic world with unique characters!\nEnjoy the fascinating RPG story!\n\n\n◆Ride your Mount and start new adventures!！◆\nGet on a Mamono, explore the world and grow stronger together!\nThe Mounts are not just monsters, but also carpets and macarons…!?\n\n\n★This game is for you if…★\n・You like MMORPG\n・You often play MMORPG games\n・You like customizing your character\n・You enjoy games where you have various Avatars\n\n\n◆Story◆\nA world where magic meets alchemy.\nIt`s the eve of the Industrial Revolution.\nPeople gather in the city\navoiding “Mamonos“,\nand the young must\ngo on an adventure.\nAnd also the Heroes\ndepart on a journey\nto defeat “Maou“ around the world\nand to find where they belong…\n\n\n★Information★\nTitle: Alchemia Story\nGenre: MMORPG that allows you to create the character you really want!\n\n\n◆Official HP: https://en.alchemiastory.jp/\n◆Official Twitter：https://twitter.com/alchemiastory\n\n\nPlease contact from ( https://en.alchemiastory.jp/contact/index/ ) if you have any concerns or inquiries.
        </item>

        <item>
           “World Boss“ New Content Update\n- Defeat powerful bosses using a total of 15 Monsters and seasonal buffs!\n- Challenge yourself to become the top Summoner and earn rewards based on your seasonal rank and grade.\n\nNew “Monster Story“ Added\n- Discover the story of the newly added Beast Rider through Monster Story!\n\nIn addition, various updates, including new symbol grades and Trial of Ascension revamp,\nawait you in 《 Summoners War: Chronicles 》!\n\n《 Game Introduction 》\n\n■ Complete the “new Summoners War story“\nProtect the kingdom against Tefo’s enormous conspiracy as a Summoner.\nImmerse yourself in the untold story of the Rahil Kingdom taking place before Sky Arena and Lost Centuria!\n\n■ 400 Types of Monsters and 5 Attributes\nSummon hundreds of Monsters, each with their own dynamic ultimate skills.\nForm a diverse team and join them on the battlefield for the first time!\n\n■ Stronger Together! “Fight Alongside Monsters“\nChoose between four Summoners, Orbia, Kina, Cleaf, and Soleta.\nExperience breathtaking battles accompanied by three Monsters.\n\n■ Explore Various Game Modes\nDelve into loot-filled Dungeons, climb the many-floored Ascensions, and take on Raids with friends!\nThen head to the Arena to compete against other players!\n\n■ Only the Strongest Survive!\nPit yourself against other players on the challenging PvP Battlefield.\nYou best come prepared.\n\n■ Gathering, Mining, and Fishing!\nTake a break from battle.\nEnjoy the natural beauty that the world has to offer.\n\n■ Team Up with Friends in “Party Play“ Co-op!\nGrab your friends to participate in public events and take on raids.\n‘Summon Your Best’ together!\n\n***\n\n[App Permissions]\nWe require permission to provide the following services while using the app.\n1. (Optional) Storage (Photos/Media/Files): Access to external storage required for additional downloads and saving in-game screenshots.\n2. (Optional) Microphone/Recording audio: Required for using voice chat\n※ Services excluding the functions related to the corresponding permissions can be used without allowing optional permissions.\n\n[How to Remove Permissions]\nYou can reset or remove permissions after allowing them as shown below.\n1. Android 6.0 or above: Settings > Apps > Select App > Permissions > Allow or Remove Permissions\n2. Android 6.0 or below: Upgrade the operating system to remove permissions or delete the app\n※ If you are using Android 6.0 or below, we recommend that you upgrade to 6.0 or above as you can`t change the optional permissions individually.\n\n• Supported Languages: 한국어, English, 日本語, 简体中文, 繁體中文, Deutsch, Français, Русский, Español, Português, Bahasa Indonesia, ไทย, Tiếng Việt, Italiano\n• This app is free-to-play and offers in-app purchases. Purchasing paid items may incur additional fees, and payment cancelation may not be available depending on the type of the item.\n• Conditions regarding the usage of this game (contract termination/payment cancelation, etc.) can be viewed in the game or the Com2uS mobile game Terms of Service (available on the website, https://terms.withhive.com/terms/policy/view/M330).\n• Inquiries regarding the game can be submitted via Com2uS Customer Support 1:1 Inquiry (http://m.withhive.com > Customer Support > 1:1 Inquiry).\n• Minimum specifications: 4GB RAM\n\n***\n- Official Brand Site: https://summonerswar.com/en/chronicles?r=p2\n- Official Forum: https://community.summonerswar.com/chronicles\n- Official YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCmGoIH-lh7dG-NWT8p1G84g
        </item>

    </string-array>

</resources>